- question: "In Ruby, variables require:"
  answer: 2
  choices:
    - A type.
    - A key word.
    - A value.
- question: "String interpolation requires:"
  answer: 2
  choices:
    - Single quotes.
    - A back slash.
    - Double quotes.
- question: "Strings:"
  answer: 0
  choices:
    - Can be added to other strings.
    - Can be added to other strings and to numbers.
    - Cannot be added.
- question: "In Chef, resource actions are:"
  answer: 1
  choices:
    - Strings.
    - Symbols.
    - Numbers.
- question: "To add new elements to the end of an array, use:"
  answer: 2
  choices:
    - '`add`.'
    - '`cat`.'
    - '`push`.'
- question: "The Chef community tends to use which method to iterate over the elements in an array:"
  answer: 1
  choices:
    - '`if`.'
    - '`each`.'
    - '`for`.'
- question: "A hash stores:"
  answer: 0
  choices:
    - Key-value pairs.
    - Strings.
    - Numbers.
- question: "In Ruby, a zero is:"
  answer: 1
  choices:
    - Falsey.
    - Truthy.
    - It depends on the code.
- question: "The simplest way to implement control flow is:"
  answer: 0
  choices:
    - '`if`.'
    - '`each`.'
    - '`for`.'
- question: "A Ruby method begins with which keyword:"
  answer: 1
  choices:
    - '`method`.'
    - '`def`.'
    - No keyword is required.
- question: "To create an instance of a class use:"
  answer: 2
  choices:
    - '`class`.'
    - '`def`.'
    - '`new`.'
- question: "Modules:"
  answer: 0
  choices:
    - Organize similar methods.
    - Are instances of a class.
    - Are used instead of classes.
